http://www.polygraphica.com/privacy-policy

Enquiry Basket - (0)
Screen Printing
New ProductsPolyflex A3 Label PressPolyflex A5 Label PressTectonic InternationalTresu - Consumables and Spare PartsDoctor Blades for Rotogravure PrintingDoctor Blades for Flexographic PrintingPMD LeasingServicesProjectsNewsContact
+44 (0) 1924 200444
|
Home > Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Polygraphica are strongly committed to protecting your privacy while interacting with our content, products and services. We want to provide a safe and secure environment for you.
Polygraphica are concerned about protecting the safety and privacy of people using our services.
The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to tell you what kind of information we may gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct this information. Our policy allows you to choose what kind and how much information you provide to us and to control how we use whatever information you give us. Our goal is to provide you with a satisfying experience while allowing you to control your privacy and to give you a means to voice any questions or concerns you may have.
Collection of information
Information is collected from you primarily to make it easier and more rewarding for you to use our services. Depending on the service you are accessing, you could be asked to provide information such as your name, email address or information about what you like and do not like. It is entirely your choice whether to respond to these questions or not.
You do not have to give us any personal data or private information about yourself to access the information on our site, unless you want to make use of Polygraphica's online services.
Our system does automatically gather certain usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors. This collective data helps us determine how much visitors use specific parts of our site, so that we can improve it and make sure that it is as accessible as we can make it for as many people as possible.
If you visit our site just to read or download information, we will collect and store only the following information about your visit:
The name of the domain from which you access the Internet, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address or host name, which does not usually identify a specific computer. The date and time you access our site. The pages you visit. The Internet address of any website from which you linked directly to our site.
This information (web access logs) does not contain any personal data or private information, and we do not make any attempt to link the information in the logs with the individuals who actually visit our site. We collect web access log information for internal monitoring only.
We will collect personal data or private information only if you specifically and knowingly provide it, through using an electronic form. When you supply any personal data or private information in this way, we have legal obligations to you in the way we deal with that data: we must explain why we are requesting the information, and then use it only for the purposes described when the information is collected. We must tell you if we want to pass the information on to anyone else. In general, any information you provide will only be accessed by authorised employees of Polygraphica. We will never share your personal data or private information without first obtaining your consent, unless we are required by law to disclose it.
Cookies
Cookies themselves are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any information that could be used to discover your identity.
We only use cookies when you are providing us with personal data or private information, such as filling in a form online. These hold only a sequential session identification number and are deleted at the end of the transaction.
Future developments may include the use of cookies to enhance our personalised services to customers, but this usage will always be optional. Users can set their computer to accept all cookies, to notify them when a cookie is issued, or not to receive any cookies at any time. The last of these options may mean that personalised services cannot then be provided to that user.
Disclosure
There will be occasions where it will be necessary for Polygraphica to disclose your personal information to third parties. Polygraphica may be required by law to disclose the information, or Polygraphica may be required to disclose your personal information to third parties to provide the service you have requested. However, the disclosure will only be made where it is necessary to fulfil the purpose for which you disclosed your personal information. Otherwise than stated above, we do not disclose personal information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any organisation or person outside Polygraphica unless you have authorised us to do so.
No sale of personal information
Under no circumstances will Polygraphica sell or receive payment for licensing or disclosing your personal information.
Access and correction: personal data
If Polygraphica holds your personal information Polygraphica will, where possible, provide you with access to the information. Polygraphica will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.
Security
Polygraphica operates secure data networks that are designed to protect your privacy and security.
Complaints about privacy
If you have any complaints relating to online privacy issues on our websites, please notify Polygraphica . While Polygraphica accepts no liability for any material or links posted to the service, we will investigate all complaints.
Changes to Online privacy policy
If we decide to change the Polygraphica Privacy Policy, we will post those changes here.
Interested in a Machine?
Contact us today by telephone on +44 (0) 1924 200444 or fill in the form.
Country
AfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBolivia (Plurinational State of)Bosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBritish Virgin IslandsBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCabo VerdeBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongoDemocratic Republic of the CongoCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzechiaCôte d'IvoireDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faeroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHondurasChina, Hong Kong Special Administrative RegionHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIran (Islamic Republic of)IraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgChina, Macao Special Administrative RegionThe former Yugoslav Republic of MacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia (Federated States of)Republic of MoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandDemocratic People's Republic of KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauState of PalestinePanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaRéunionSamoaSan MarinoSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint Maarten (Dutch part)SlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaRepublic of KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Martin (French part)Saint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicSao Tome and PrincipeTajikistanUnited Republic of TanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUnited States Virgin IslandsUnited Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern IrelandUnited States of AmericaUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuHoly SeeVenezuela (Bolivarian Republic of)Viet NamWallis and Futuna IslandsWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands
Browse through our database of quality used printing, packaging and converting equipment.
View Machines
Looking to Buy?
Add machinery free of charge to our database or contact us to discuss the sale for you.
Contact Us
Looking to Sell?
Subscribe to our newsletter for the latest machinery and stocklists updates:
